# Zaryab Khan

### Computer Scientist

My objective is to pursue a career in project management by ensuring that the standards and specifications are met in order to generate maximum investment returns. I will do this by implementing management techniques, appropriate control, risk management strategies, and conflict intervention in collaboration with my team. I hold two years of experience in diverse set of industries such as banking, medical and logistic.



zaryabkhan864@gmail.com

Marachi, Pakistan

S zaryabkhan864@gmail.com

(+92)3312226527 / (+90)5528421868

in linkedin.com/in/zaryabkhan864

# **EDUCATION**

# Masters In Computer Science (MSCS)

Altinbas University / Istanbul, Turkey

09/2020 - Present

CGPA 3.75

# **Bachelor's In Computer Science**

Usman Institute of Technology / Karachi, Pakistan

2013 - 2018

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Software Engineer

# Digitaez

12/2021 - Present Karachi

Digitaez is a software house located in pakistan karachi working different technologies

#### Tasks

 Developing different websites and web applications on multiple platfoams such as reactis, node js, html, css, javascript

### Software Engineer

### Denim Prive

01/2021 - 06/2021 karachi

Denim prive is one of the best garment company in pakistan

#### Tasks

 Developing garments ERP based on ASP.net and Microsoft server 2019 and Telerik framework for frontend, Created foams, and reports

# Service desk officer

### Tabba Heart Hospital / Karachi, Pakistan

09/2017 - 12/2020

karachi

THI is one of the highest ranked hospital of Pakistan, established in the year 2005 emphasizing in offering Cardiac treatment and services

#### Tasks

 Supporting hospital ERP "HOPE", understanding and analyzing ERP, addresses the end users queries and support issues. Also identify bugs and report to SKM (Shaukat khanum hospital)

### Internee

### Dubai Islamic bank / Karachi, Pakistan

07/2015 - 08/2015

karachi

Dubai Islamic bank is international bank based on Dubai which works according to Internal Sharia Supervisory Committee ("ISSC") .

#### Tasks

 worked on banking ERP, Creating foams using PLSQL and also worked on Oracle database 9i

# SKILLS

<u>Oracle</u> 9i, 10g, 11g

C+

C#

sp.net

SQL, PLSql

Javascript

React

SQL Server 2019

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap

MS Office

Basic Knowledge of Networking

# PERSONAL PROJECTS

#### Turkish Website

- A Turkish based company "Nanse Group" www.nansegroup.com
- It is a static website developed on HTML,CSS,JavaScript,Bootstrap

#### Capture Perfect (09/2016 - 09/2017)

- Programming Language Android
- Capture perfect is based on social activities. It can be most helpful for athletes, adventures, professional racers, so its aim is to provide quality images and videos with ease, to increase productivity among social apps and also provide hands free environment.

#### School Management System (SMS) (06/2013 - 08/2013)

- Programming Language PLSQL, SQL
- Database (Oracle 9i)
- SMS has developed on oracle 9i. It has student registration module, teacher's registration module, Academic modules, finance modules also reporting of student grades, attendance, fees voucher.

### RAA (Website) (2018)

- Progamming Language -Html, CSS, PHP, Javascript, Bootstrap.
- Tools xammp, VS code, PYPAdmin
- It has home page, Gas and electricity, Partner pages
- It also complain and request foams
- Partner can logging on website and send the quotation to clients

#### Save Message Transfer (2016)

- tool- Cisco Packet tracer
- Protocols OSPF, EIGRP
- Access list
- Topology- Star

#### Blood Bank Management System (Desktop Application)

- Programming Language- C#
- Tool Visual Studio 2015
- Database Sql Server 2012
- It has patient registration, staff, hospital registration module
- Maintaining the blood stock and test result module, It can create the procedure reports

# WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Internee

# Qasim International Container Terminal (QICT)

07/2014 - 09/2014

Karachi

DP World is Multinational firm located in 103 countries operate as a global trade enabler.

#### Tasks

 Worked on logistics ERP and developing new foams and reports based on oracle using the plsql and also worked on oracle database 9i

#### Internee

# Excloud software house / Karachi, Pakistan

01/2014 - 04/2017

Karachi

#### Tasks

 Worked on different websites such as restaurants, Blogs, Gas and electricity product selling website.

# **EXTRA CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES**

Worked in Promed Hair transplant center, Istanbul Turkey (09/2020 - 02/2021)

Give the awareness about products and hair transplant procedure to our international clients.

Winner in All UIT cricket tournament (2017)

Winner in Table Tennis Tournament (2018)

# **CERTIFICATES**

Managing Big Data with MySQL (06/2020)

Programming for Everybody (Getting Started with Python) (08/2020)

Mobile Computing Workshop (Andriod) (10/2015)

Network Simulations Workshop using OPNET (09/2015)

# **LANGUAGES**

Enalish

Professional Working Proficiency

Urdu

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Turkish

Professional Working Proficiency

# **INTERESTS**

Music

**Book Reading** 

Travelling

Game